wp-rocket.me 2019-07-23

# Privacy Policy - WP Rocket

Your privacy really matters. At WP Media, we have a few fundamental principles :

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the ongoing operation of one of our services.
  * We don’t sell any of your personal information

Below is our privacy policy, which incorporates these goals.

This policy has been largely inspired by [Automattic privacy policy](https://automattic.com/privacy/), and is available under a Creative Commons ShareAlike license, which means you’re more than welcome to steal it and repurpose it for your own use.

WP Media operates several websites including wp-rocket.me, imagify.io, wp-media.me It is WP Media’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please contact our support.

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, WP Media collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request.

WP Media purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how WP Media’s visitors use its website. From time to time, WP Media may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

WP Media also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on WP Media’s website.

## Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to WP Media’s websites choose to interact with WP Media in ways that require WP Media to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that WP Media gathers depends on the nature of the interaction.

For example, we ask visitors who buy a licence for WP Rocket to provide email address, country, name, and financial information required to process those transactions. WP Media collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with WP Media.

WP Media does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

WP Media discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on WP Media’s behalf or to provide services available at WP Media’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others.

Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using WP Media’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. WP Media will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone.

Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, WP Media discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when WP Media believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of WP Media, third parties or the public at large.

If you are a registered user of an WP Media website and have supplied your email address, WP Media may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with WP Media and our products.

We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users.

WP Media takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns.

WP Media uses cookies to help WP Media identify and track visitors, their usage of WP Media website, and their website access preferences.

WP Media visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using WP Media’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of WP Media’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

## Business Transfers

If WP Media, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that WP Media goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party.

You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of WP Media may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

## Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies.

These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer.

This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you.

This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by WP Media and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, WP Media may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in WP Media’s sole discretion.

WP Media encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us by email : [contact@wp-rocket.me](mailto:contact@wp-rocket.me)
